http://www.heritagelivingtrust.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Is a Living Trust Right For You?
Learn more by listening to a 9 Minute, Toll-Free, Telephone Living Trust Presentation
Call (866) 927-8552 x1 (also in Spanish x2)
What People Are Saying About Heritage Trust
"I have a close personal friend, who is now 90 years old. She had a trust from Heritage Living Trust created about 3 years ago and since that time has been diagnosed with dementia. A week ago, after checking herself out of the hospital, the public guardian filed for conservatorship, asking the probate court to appoint them, the public guardian, as her new caregiver/conservator. My friend has no family left, but due to her Trust which was created while she was of sound mind, declared her wishes as to who she wanted to serve as her conservator if the time ever came to when she would need to be conserved. Normally, a non-relative conservatorship would be fairly difficult to implement, but in this case, the named individual in her estate plan came to the court and told the court that they desire to serve as my friend's conservator and will accept that responsibility. This morning, the probate attorney and the public guardian agreed that the named individual in the estate plan created by Heritage has precedence, and that the trust was sufficient to place that individual as her conservator.
If it were not for her Heritage trust, she would be another case added to the already overloaded government workers conservatorship pile. Instead, an individual who she loves, and who loves her, is now fulfilling my friend's final wishes and providing for her the end of life care that she deserves after having worked hard for the past 90 years."
R. Jones...California
---
"Thank you Heritage Staff and Associates for providing the type of customer service a consumer only dreams of. I am so impressed with the accurate and timely response to my many questions and how everything is explained in terms I can understand. Most impressive is the ability to make changes to our trust at any time without an extra charge. I am confident that Heritage Trust has given me the security my family needs for the future." Z. Gibbs...Colorado
- - -
"In 2003 when I was looking for someone to do my Living Trust, I found HeritageLivingTrust.com . I met with the staff at their office and we started the process. The service was and is above and beyond my expectations. In 2007, after marrying again, my husband and I had them set up a new A-B Trust, which we have amended several times since then, at no extra cost. We have been completely satisfied and send them Kudos for all their patience, hard work and professionalism." Chris and George S., Pacific Grove, California
Other Resources
Safe and Secure Assets
Tax Schemes that Don't Work
Probate Schedules by State
Blog Index
Conservatorship...Why It Is So Important Peace of Mind Joint Tenancy and Capital Gains Limited Reach of the Estate Tax The Attorney Who Defends Himself Is A Fool New 2013 Estate Tax Changes How To Deal with Difficult Family Situations Three Disasters You Don't Want To Experience I Have A Sure Fire Cure For Cancer A Living Trust Would Have Prevented These Situations...Consider Them Carefully!
Navigation
Links
Probate Schedules by State
Free Living Will
Agents
Cecilia
InsuranceAdvisors
bohays
Piland
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Heritage Living Trust. this privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the folowing:
1. What personaly identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your date.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. the computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure invironment
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 888-437-8778 or via email
Copyright © 2020, Heritage Living Trust.
All rights reserved.
